flashcarddb.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy - Internet Flashcard Database

FlashcardDB (the "Internet Flashcard Database") (the "site") provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally-identifying information received from users of this website. It is FlashcardDB's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect. Although most changes are likely to be minor, FlashcardDB may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. FlashcardDB encourages visitors to check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Website Visitors

Like most websites, FlashcardDB collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. FlashcardDB's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how FlashcardDB's visitors use the Site. From time to time, FlashcardDB may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the site.

FlashcardDB also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. FlashcardDB does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to the FlashcardDB website choose to interact with FlashcardDB in ways that require FlashcardDB to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that FlashcardDB gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who wish to have the ability to reset their password or who wish to receive notifications of expired cards waiting to be studied at FlashcardDB to provide an e-mail address. In each case, FlashcardDB collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with FlashcardDB. FlashcardDB does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

FlashcardDB may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the site. For instance, FlashcardDB may monitor the most popular parts of the site. FlashcardDB may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, FlashcardDB does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

FlashcardDB discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on FlashcardDB's behalf or to provide services available at the FlashcardDB website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using FlashcardDB's services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. FlashcardDB will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, FlashcardDB discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when FlashcardDB believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of FlashcardDB, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of FlashcardDB and have supplied your email address, FlashcardDB may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with FlashcardDB or our related products. We primarily use our blog or Twitter to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. FlashcardDB takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the site each time the visitor returns. FlashcardDB uses cookies to help FlashcardDB identify and track visitors, their usage of FlashcardDB, and their site access preferences. FlashcardDB visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies (in general or specifically from FlashcardDB) before using the FlashcardDB website, with the drawback that certain features of the site may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

We also use third party advertising companies (such as the Google AdSense program) on FlashcardDB to serve ads when you visit the site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
